[music]
I want to be a Jag. I want to win games
with the Jags. I want to win a Super
Bowl with the Jags. I want to do it all.
days at [music] these prospects and now
Jaguars will never forget. The 2026 NFL
draft from the confluence in Pittsburgh
is in the books and the Jaguars
draft room is empty. The hay is in the
barn, so to speak. All the picks are in.
The undrafted free agency is underway.
We'll see what they come up with there
in the coming days. Welcome in to our
draft rap show. JP Shadrick with you and
our entire crew after the Jaguars put
together the 2026 draft with 10 picks.
John Oer with us now, jaguars.com senior
writer. And here we go again. John,
another one of these drafts in the
books. It's always it's it was a
different vibe obviously with no first
round pick this year and then having to
wait and be patient for Jaguars fans,
but they've got some guys to fill out
the depth of this roster and compete in
some key spots.
>> Yeah. and a patience was the watch word.
And when James Gladstone spoke to the
media just now, he he said, "Look,
that's a big part of who he is as a
drafter. Likes numbers. Uh 10 draft
picks, likes to lean into that. The more
at bats, the better success. And uh as
we said through the weekend, uh this is
a draft that coupled with last year,
coupled with next year, is going to be
the core of this regime. Uh, this was
number two out of probably three that's
going to form the core and it was a
methodical building block draft.
>> We'll hear from Liam Cohen coming up.
We'll hear from Bucky Brooks coming up
in Los Angeles in just a little bit.
Let's hear from the GM James Gladstone.
They added 10 players in the draft and
he's with Kai Stevens.
>> James, all wrapped up with the 2026
draft class. Uh, we know you like to be
bold. That's a statement you always like
to make. Obviously trading for Travis
Hunter last year that was clear. or do
you feel like you were bold with your
picks this year?
>> You know, I'd tag it as strategically
bold. We wanted to attack the volume
play as best we could while at the same
time prioritizing the players that we
felt like could uh level up our team
moving forward and really excited about
the outcome and the results and look
forward to these guys each getting a
shot to hit the ground running when they
arrive here in a couple weeks.
>> Heard you say Duvall DNA. Do you feel
like this class embodies that to you and
what does that mean? Yeah, I think in a
real way it does and it's something that
we really spend a lot of energy on
curating and tracking and you know at
each pickpoint. It's really what's top
of mind and ensuring that we don't drift
too far from it. But ultimately it's
many of the things that I've [snorts]
spoke about before, right? The
intangibly rich elements that oftent
times aren't surface level but lie
beneath the hood uh are the things that
we're trying to lean into and uh with
each of these guys it it certainly
stands out. had a fairly even split uh
offense, defense, but some similarities
in some of the picks, obviously
captains, experienced players, transfers
that were successful in a second
location. Um do you feel like you kind
of rounded things out in a way where you
have all the attributes you like and
some versatility?
>> Yeah, I think that's definitely a big
piece to the puzzle and ultimately, you
know, the idea with age and experience
that can be a really good thing. Guys
walk in the door and they have uh a bit
quicker of a runway. you know, there's
not uh so much uh development that's
required as much as it is readymade to a
degree. And uh certainly looking forward
to these guys all getting the the shot
to level up our team and knowing that
each of them is essentially made up of
all the right stuff that when they enter
this environment that they can thrive in
it and be the best version of whatever
their capacity actually is. So there's a
lot of alignment there.
>> And your day wasn't done when the picks
were done. Obviously get the undrafted
guys in here as well. You saw some
significant contributions from some of
the guys last year. Do you are you
hopeful with the class that you're able
to bring in this year you can see some
of the same?
>> Yeah, we're still rounding that out and
I know uh a part of the delay and even
getting over here was a lot of those
conversations and you know you can't
really get going there until uh the last
pick is in and so uh ultimately we're
we're happy about where things are
trending there and know that there are
plenty of people that are going to be
competing for spots and uh you know and
nothing changes with what we're
prioritizing in that space in comparison
to what we do at each draft day
selection. So, same type of human beings
are the ones that we're uh prioritizing
and the same elements that we lean into
with those elections is what we're
leaning into with those signings.
>> Thank you, James.
>> I appreciate it. Till the next one.
>> Indeed, James Gladstone, general manager
with Kai Stevens. More from Kai coming
up shortly. Let's get to the picks.
Let's go through them. For the first
time in franchise history, though, no
first round selection. There was
speculation of trying to back in to the
round, but ended up not happening. So,
it's on to day two. The Jaguars tried to
move up, made some calls, but they
stayed where they were and added tight
end Nate Boracher from Texas A&M who
visited with the Jags media after the
pick.
>> You know how it is. It's with the with
the spam stuff coming up. I saw um a
random number. It said spam on there and
uh I didn't know what to do. I showed my
agent. He said, "Better answer it." So
So I answered it and my heart sunk. Um
man, it's crazy.
>> Yeah, heart sunk in a good way. Number
56 overall. John, you know, he's played
a lot of football. Kind of a blocking
style tight end. Not a lot of big
statistics with this one, but he will be
valuable for Liam Cohen's offense.
>> Yeah, look, uh, this surprised some
people, but the Jaguars needed to get
some building done at the tight end
position. Plays into something else that
happened today. But, um, he is a guy who
will fit with Brenton Strange and give
the offense a wrinkle that they wanted
and didn't have [music] with some
heavier tight ends, some multiple tight
end. uh following a league trend, but
it's something they feel like can take
advantage of the defenses. He's a huge
part of that.
>> Yeah, big physical guy as well and you
know, mature. He's about about to be 25
years old in the month of September. So,
a valuable piece. Now, on to the third
round for the Jaguars. They entered with
three picks in that round and stayed
with them all starting at 81 overall
with Texas A&M defensive tackle Albert
Regis. And his daughter, I think, knew
it all along.
She was like, "Hey, I got this idea.
Let's let Akari, you know, put out some
cups. Let's let her crawl what she
thinks." And I was like, "Whatever."
Like I don't really not whatever in a
bad in a way of like I don't care, but
like I like sure. I like why not. And
then I go and play the game and then her
family's in town. So they all did it and
I'm watching in the background and then
every time they're like, "She went to
Jacksonville. She went to Jacksonville.
She went to Jacksonville." And I was
like, "Well, since the end of the season
I've been saying Duvall is where I want
to be." And She went three times and
then it was just like
well I was like God is it's written in
the books. I was God never lies. He
never does wrong. And I mean I'm here
and it's just amazing.
>> It certainly is fantastic story there. A
disruptor on the interior. We talked
about it going into this draft. John,
this is just what the Jaguars needed. A
penetrator inside.
>> Yeah. And I don't know if he had the
sack number of a penetrating guy, but
he's got the film and he's got the
ability to go side to side. He has that
athleticism. Look, this team believes in
being good on both lines, being
physical, being strong up front. He fits
into that.
>> Now, seven picks later, 88th overall to
the offensive line for the Jacksonville
Jaguars with guard Emanuel Pregnon from
Oregon. Was with Southern California and
then Wyoming before that. And what a
celebration for his family.
>> [screaming]
>> Yeah, I'd say they're happy, John. And
you know what? The Jaguars should be
happy as well. Interior offensive line.
And to your point all the time, if
you're going to develop the offensive
line, you better start drafting the
offensive line. Yeah, you have to. And
if you're going to be good in these
rounds in the offensive line, you need
to draft him a year out. I don't know if
he pushes for a starting job this year
or not. I don't think this team, you
know, they love that, but they don't
care. [music] Um, he is a guy who along
with Wyatt Milm probably forms the core
of the interior line going forward. As
Liam Cohen said last night, I'm
paraphrasing a little bit, anytime
you're telling him that you're getting
bigger, strong guys up front, he's
happy. So, uh, and guess what? EVP's
happy, too.
>> Yeah. And Jonah Manheim, his teammate at
Southern California, is happy as well.
Some young offensive linemen for the
Jaguars. And finally, on Friday night,
the final pick of the third round. The
Jaguars go back on defense. Safety
Jaylen Husky from Maryland. And he was
in a unique place when he got the news.
[screaming]
>> I'M TELLING YOU, I'M TELLING YOU, I'M
[screaming] TELLING YOU, MAN.
THEY TALKING ABOUT,
[screaming]
[groaning]
>> you know, it's hard to tell his Top Golf
score from all the the yelling and the
celebration there. I'm sure they weren't
worried about that last night.
Unbelievable player, though.
>> Yeah, that was good stuff. That was uh
I'm not sure I've quite seen a draft uh
reaction video quite like that. Uh he's
a hitter and can also force turnovers.
Jaguars like playing two or three
safeties back there. They now have four
or five who can play back there. Uh
that's a pick that I wouldn't be
surprised makes an impact this year.
>> And a lot of those guys on the back end
of the secondary are, you know, first
contract, young players on this team
still.
>> Young players who can catch the ball.
>> Absolutely.
>> They like that.
>> Absolutely. Now on to day number three
and round number four. for the Jaguars
moved up five spots to select Duke
defensive end Wesley Williams.
Yes, an edge player, a pass rusher. He
can do a whole lot more than that. He
caught up with Kai Stevens.
>> Yeah, I think that versatility um just
being able to make and affect the game
um wherever I'm at, you know, whether
it's special teams, inside, outside,
online scrimmage, even dropping into
coverage. I feel like as long as I can
affect winning in a spot, that's where I
want to be, you know.
>> Yeah, he's all over the place for this.
Look at from the sideline making tackles
on the edge and then of course in the
pass rush game against tackles in the
run defense he can do it all. John,
>> he hits and he's not just a pass rusher.
Uh he can play the run a little bit.
This team values that. Uh I think they
this was a position they wanted to get
done somewhere in the first four or five
rounds. Maybe waited a little longer
than they at than they wanted to at this
spot, but they like him. uh especially
the physicality and the ability to
develop and start getting to the
quarterback and maybe even as a rookie
combined with BJ Green Strago, they've
got some young guys there. Uh a lot of
at bats at that position to figure out
who can line up there and allow Trayvon
Walker to move inside a little bit.
>> You can never have enough of those guys
because the two undrafted guys last year
that you mentioned contributed towards
the end of the season in a big way for
this defense. Now on to the fifth round.
164 overall for the Jaguars. Tight end
Tanner Kosio out of Houston. Four years
at Ball State. One of the most
productive pass catchers in all of
college football regardless of position
the last two years, John. And now two
tight ends and one draft for the Jags.
>> Well, it's first time it's ever
happened. And it absolutely uh for the
Jaguars, meaning first time they've ever
drafted two. And it wasn't like they
drafted one early and then won in the
seventh round as a flyer. They expect
this guy to contribute. He's another guy
who had production in college, caught a
lot of passes. He's used to success,
used to catching the ball, did it at two
different schools. So, um, look, they
wanted to have tight ends who can play.
They now have Quinton Morris, Brenton
Strange, two in this draft. Uh,
you don't always get the obvious theme
of the draft every year. The obvious
theme of this year's draft, Jaguars and
NFL, the league is moving toward this
concept of a lot of tight ends playing a
lot of roles on a lot of plays.
>> And he's a mismatch, too. 6'6, 250
pounds can be a real problem anywhere on
the field, but especially in the red
zone. Now, for the rest of the picks, a
pair of wide receivers in the sixth
round for the Jaguars. They traded with
the Patriots to move up to 191 for
Baylor wide receiver Josh Cameron. one
of the best players in the Big 12 the
last two years. 19 touchdowns those two
seasons combined and has some return
specialist game as well. Then at 203
overall, Stanford receiver CJ Williams
one year at Southern California, two
years as was at Wisconsin mainly as a
reserve there and then led Stanford in
receptions, receiving yards and
receiving touchdowns last year. Then a
pair of seventh round picks both on
defense. Defensive end Zack Dery from
Washington, two years at Sou Falls. Last
three years in Seattle, a regular
starter finally last year for the
Huskies and at 240 overall. Middle
Tennessee State linebacker Parker
Hughes. He's a speedster. Ran a 4.3940
at the proday. 5 years in Murreey'sboro,
Tennessee. And he's light, he's fast,
and he is productive. We welcome in NFL
Network analyst and Jaguars sideline
reporter and our host on Huddle Up with
Bucky Brooks. It's Bucky Brooks joining
us after the 2026 NFL draft. Let's start
with the big themes for the Jaguars. No
first round pick. Patience was key for
James Gladstone. What did you make of
the hall overall for this draft class?
>> Yeah, know I think a lot of this will be
determined in a few years when we look
back and see how these guys perform. But
I do like uh the players that we brought
in and I know the outside noise has been
loud uh because the Jaguars stuck to
their guts. They had conviction about
the players that they got and even
though it didn't match consensus outside
opinion, I think James Gladstone kind of
explained what it is that they wanted.
They wanted guys who were captains, guys
who had experience, guys who were
versatile, and they wanted guys who had
a quick runway to the field because they
were readymade. The other thing, J uh
John already alluded to it, the tight
end situation. As the league is catching
up to what the Rams did with multiple
tight ends and 13 personnel, the Jaguars
clearly had a point of making sure that
they wanted a blocking tight end,
multiple blocking tight ends, and
multiple flex tight ends to be able to
assemble a variety of different
personnel groupings to challenge the
defense in a few different ways. And
Becky, I know there's a lot with the
draft, a lot of players, but I'm
fascinated and it's such a theme of the
draft, the tight end thing. Uh, if
they're successful in sort of being able
to use that package, how does this
complement what's already a very uh
potent offense? It feels like it just
gives it another wrinkle that could make
it even harder to stop.
>> Yeah, it makes it very, very difficult.
So, you have to understand trends from
the defensive side to then be able to
build something on the offensive side
that can counter that. So defensively, a
lot of teams are sitting in two high
safeties and they're daring people to
run the football. They're daring people
to uh take a slow, patient approach to
drive the ball down the field. Part of
this is due to Vic Fangio's success
running these two high looks with light
boxes and those things. Well, when you
put more tight ends on the field, you
either are going to run rough shot over
those fronts and those soft packages.
Um, or you're going to force the defense
to match up in various ways that you can
eventually exploit by bringing in the
tight ends that they're bringing in
while still having Brett and Strange as
a part of this. You are creating all
kinds of chaos for the defense. They
have to decide, do we want to go big on
big? Do we want to stay in our base
package? Do we want to go nickel? And
all of those things have, I would say,
uh, potential to be exploited based on
the talent of that personnel. I really
like what they're doing, but it's
something that the rest of the league is
doing. And so, from a defensive
standpoint, the Jags have to prepare for
it, but offensively, it could be very
advantageous with all these big bodies
on the field. Bucky Brooks with us. A
couple more for you, Bucky, before we
get you out of here. I know it's been a
long weekend. Certainly, the defensive
pickups for the Jaguars starting with
Regis at the defensive tackle spot.
Jaylen Husky at safety. What stands out
about those players? How can they fit
into the rotation at least on defense?
>> Look, I'm gonna say this and I think you
have to add Wesley Williams because I
had a chance to watch him at the East
West Shrine game. Um, what they're doing
is they're bringing quality depth and
Reges, you're talking about an athletic
uh interior player who is active hands,
very physical, loves to get after it.
When Glastone talks about guys who kind
of fit that Duvall [music] DNA, he
certainly is a part of that and that is
the passion, the love for the game, but
more importantly the effort with which
he plays. You see him there doing the
army crawl after it. He gets after it.
So you like that. Jaylen Husky, another
safety that kind of fits the profile.
You look at Antonio Johnson and some of
the other guys in the back end, man,
they're active. They have great
instincts. They're aware. They don't
mind hitting, but they're always around
the ball. And we talk about a defense
that lived on the turnover because there
was a natural turnover obsession. You
have to have those guys that specialize
in taking the ball away to take the ball
away at the pro level. And then finally,
I want to talk about Wesley Williams
because Wesley Williams played at a
school down the road for my alma mater.
I I won't talk about the school name,
but I'll talk about the the energy and
the physicality that he brings. He was
one of the best players at the East West
Shrine. Dominated uh the practice week.
[music] And then when you go back and
you look at his regular season tape, you
see him the effort, the energy, the
physicality. If you really look at the
players that the Jags bought in, there's
a style of play that you can see that we
are trying to establish. Physicality,
toughness is at the forefront of
everything that these guys have. And
when you put that together, you have a
team and a locker room full of those
guys. We begin to recreate the edge that
Liam Cohen has talked about playing
with. Uh, I like it. And I also like it
because if you look around the division
at what the Tennessee Titans have done,
which the hu Houston Texans have done,
and even the Indianapolis Colts,
everybody in the division has got a
little rougher and tougher. You better
have a team that can buckle up. And the
Jaguars certainly have drafted guys that
kind of fit that mantra.
>> Yes, Duke is pretty good at football
these days. Even though you won't say
the name of the school, Bucky, that's
okay.
>> I don't I don't I didn't even know it
had a name. I just know it's eight miles
down the road and they wear a different
color blue.
>> Fair enough. Bucky, it's been a long
weekend. Appreciate your contributions
as always. We'll talk to you on
Wednesday for Huddle Up. Appreciate it,
man.
>> Hey, man. Talk to you soon.
>> Bucky Brooks out of here from NFL
Network. You know, head coach Liam Cohen
is part of this obviously as 10 drafted
players added to his locker room. Couple
weeks away from rookie mini camp, but
he's with Kai Stevens.
>> Liam, this is your second draft class
here in Jacksonville. We've heard that
Duvall DNA word a lot or thrown around a
bit this week. what does that mean to
you and and what does this class kind of
embody that for you?
>> Yeah, so much of that is um put together
through the the players makeup, his
personal character, his football
character and uh continuing to try to
bring in those type of players and to
add uh to the culture in the locker room
and getting guys that are super
competitive that love football, they
love to compete and the process that
goes along with it. So, it's always at
the forefront of every pick that we make
and um you know, you're you're trying to
challenge the locker room, challenge it
with both both on the field and off the
field.
>> Uh obviously had to wait a little bit
little bit longer. You're used to that.
Jacksonville fans aren't. They've never
not had a first round pick before, but
do you still look at the guys that
you're able to get as potential starters
or do you see them more as contributors
that might eventually become a starter?
>> Yeah, I think that's the beauty of it is
that uh it can kind of become anything,
right? is that competition breeds
excellence and um you try to get players
in here that you feel like are going to
compete with the guys that are here and
uh while also knowing you feel really
good about the team you have and I think
that's a cool position to be in to not
have to necessarily reach for any
specific position. Um that that's fun
that makes it a fun draft and for you to
be able to go and kind of find the guys
that you feel like you want in this
building as a collective. And we had so
much uh consistency through coaching and
scouting with so many of these guys we
were able to bring in this draft that
there's a lot of heat for a lot of these
guys that are coming in.
>> Got two tight ends. Uh what are you
excited about doing with them on
offense?
>> I think um you know we felt some pains
last year when we were only had two
tight ends active for I think it was a
three-game stretch. Uh having to utilize
the jumbo tackle a little bit to to help
with that. Well, that that's not exactly
what you're trying to do, right? When
you want to run the football, you want
to be able to have a balance and and the
defense to be on their toes to not know
if you're going to run it or pass the
ball. So, uh adding to that room,
creating more depth and competition and
with two guys that, you know, we think
Bour and and Kosil are very different in
a lot of ways, but also have some
similar traits. And so, um, I think that
position being so important to football
in general, but also to our building.
>> I I know you mentioned this a little
bit, some of these guys, captains, you
know, five-year guys, maybe a transfer,
had some success there. Those are key
traits for you, but also versatility
seems like was something that was big
for you and and contributions on special
teams.
>> Absolutely. You look at um some of the
trends in the NFL recently with some of
the 13 personnel and bigger packages.
Well, on defense, how do you continue to
combat that? Well, making sure that you
have diversity and multiplicity within,
especially at that safety position,
right? Having the ability to have
Antonio Johnson go down and play big
nickel while also making sure that you
have depth at the true safety position.
And so, so much of that flexibility and
allowing guys, whether it's linebackers
that can maybe go back and play stack or
can also go on the line of scrimmage and
rush. So, some of those things are
really important to us. I think uh
continuing to be flexible and diverse is
is something we appreciate.
>> Thanks, coach.
>> Thank you.
>> Thanks to head coach Liam Cohen, of
course, Kai Stevens all weekend long for
all the interviews after the picks here
on our coverage. Uh John, second draft
class for James Gladstone checked the
box in a in a good way, I think.
>> Yeah. And you know, something Liam said
really stood out as the second theme.
You know, Gladstone talked a lot today
about volume and liking at bats. Uh,
I've been around a lot of teams. Every
team says they want to be tough. They
want to be physical.
>> This team clearly puts it foremost and
makes sure that they check that box with
every pick. Uh, that's not always easy
to do. No,
>> it's not always easy. It's not always
easy to stick to that theme. Uh they are
every time they acquire, every time they
have a wave of acquisition, they get
more toward that. They were tough last
year, they're going to get tougher going
forward.
>> John, great stuff as always. Appreciate
it. Another We did it again.
>> We did it again.
>> We did it again. Uh our entire crew did
it again as well. all sides of our
coverage from football operations, the
PR staff, of course, social, digital
media, our graphics folks, all our
camera operators, everybody behind the
scenes, our whole production department.
Uh, it's a big weekend for us here at
jaguars.com. We appreciate all their
contributions. We certainly thank you
for watching as well. For John Oer, for
Kai Stevens, our entire crew, I'm JP
Shadrich saying good night. Here is the
hall. All the picks for the Jacksonville
Jaguars in the 2026 NFL draft.